https://therealnews.com/privacy-policy#cookie-policy

Close
Donate
Search for:
RSS Feed
Help Make Real News! Donate Now!
The Marc Steiner Show
Sign up for our Newsletter!
Email address:
YouTube
Search for:
Search
Trending Posts
200K wrongfully purged GA voters fight to be heard in Senate runoffs
A statement from The Real News
Obama slams 'Defund the Police,' but his failed reforms fueled the movement
Was Andrés Guardado the target of a police gang initiation?
Securitizing climate change can lead to more surveillance and eco-fascism
College athletes sacrificed as universities focus on profits; Biden’s economic plans come up short
He bought a car at police auction and got arrested for what was in it
Cabinet of the living dead
Pentagon Engaged in Unfathomable Financial Mismanagement
Obama knows something about slogans that disappoint people
Close
Help Make Real News! Donate Now!
The Marc Steiner Show
Sign up for our Newsletter!
Email address:
YouTube
Search for:
Search
Trending Posts
200K wrongfully purged GA voters fight to be heard in Senate runoffs
A statement from The Real News
Obama slams 'Defund the Police,' but his failed reforms fueled the movement
Was Andrés Guardado the target of a police gang initiation?
Securitizing climate change can lead to more surveillance and eco-fascism
College athletes sacrificed as universities focus on profits; Biden’s economic plans come up short
He bought a car at police auction and got arrested for what was in it
Cabinet of the living dead
Pentagon Engaged in Unfathomable Financial Mismanagement
Obama knows something about slogans that disappoint people
Skip to content
Dear Members, Supporters and Viewers of The Real News Network,
We are sending out this message to update our current privacy policy in light of the new GDRP Privacy Rules initiated by The European Union that go into effect this month.  Our supporters are extremely important to us and therefore, so is their data.
TRNN Privacy Policy
This policy applies to all information received by TRNN, both online and offline, across any platform, including electronic, written, or oral communications.
What Data does TRNN Collect?
TRNN collects and maintains the following data:
Contact Information: name, address, telephone number, email addressGiving History: gift amount, date, any gift restrictions requested by the donorInformation on events attended, publications received, any special requests for program informationBrowser data including information about your operating system, hardware data, and browser version when submitting online forms.
TRNN does not store the following data:
Payment information including credit card numbers or bank accounts.
Online Data Transmission – New Website
All data transmitted between you and the TRNN website is now SSL encrypted.
Data Storage
All data about our donors (see list above) is stored using Raiser’s Edge NXT, a cloud-based software developed for nonprofit fundraising.  For more information regarding the data policies of Raiser’s Edge, you can visit https://www.blackbaud.com/general-data-protection-regulation.
All donation transaction data is processed and stored by Click & Pledge, an online fundraising platform for nonprofits.  For more information regarding the data policies of Click & Pledge please visit https://clickandpledge.com/privacy/
Data Usage
Donor information collected by TRNN and stored using the above mentioned methods is also used to analyze giving patterns in order to make accurate budget projections.
Browser data is only used for website diagnostic purposes
TRNN will use confidential donor information for the following purposes:
Distributing donation receiptsSending thank you letters to donorsInforming donors of TRNN news and eventsInternal analysis and record keepingContacting donors about changes to in policy
Use and Disclosure of your Personal Information:
We will not sell, share, or trade your personal information with other entities without your permission.We will not send you mailings on behalf of other organizations.We may collect your name, email address, telephone number, and payment information when you make a contribution, either on our website, over the phone, at an event, or by mailing in a check.
Consent
Your continued use of offline and online features of TRNN relating to your data will let us know that you’ve accepted these updates to our privacy policy.
The Right to be Forgotten
If you have questions about this TRNN Privacy Policy, or if you wish to be removed from our databases, please contact our Data Privacy Officer at stephenrfrank@therealnews.com.
Future Changes to TRNN Privacy Policy
We reserve the right to change this TRNN Privacy Policy in order to provide you with the best possible data security practices.  When we do, we will note the last update at the bottom of the policy.
Cookie Policy
This is the Cookie Policy for The Real News Network, accessible from https://therealnews.com
What Are Cookies
As is common practice with almost all professional websites this site uses cookies, which are tiny files that are downloaded to your computer, to improve your experience. This page describes what information they gather, how we use it and why we sometimes need to store these cookies. We will also share how you can prevent these cookies from being stored however this may downgrade or ‘break’ certain elements of the sites functionality.
For more general information on cookies, please read “What Are Cookies”.
How We Use Cookies
We use cookies for a variety of reasons detailed below. Unfortunately in most cases there are no industry standard options for disabling cookies without completely disabling the functionality and features they add to this site. It is recommended that you leave on all cookies if you are not sure whether you need them or not in case they are used to provide a service that you use.
Disabling Cookies
You can prevent the setting of cookies by adjusting the settings on your browser (see your browser Help for how to do this). Be aware that disabling cookies will affect the functionality of this and many other websites that you visit. Disabling cookies will usually result in also disabling certain functionality and features of the this site. Therefore it is recommended that you do not disable cookies.
The Cookies We Set
Account related cookies If you create an account with us then we will use cookies for the management of the signup process and general administration. These cookies will usually be deleted when you log out however in some cases they may remain afterwards to remember your site preferences when logged out.Login related cookies We use cookies when you are logged in so that we can remember this fact. This prevents you from having to log in every single time you visit a new page. These cookies are typically removed or cleared when you log out to ensure that you can only access restricted features and areas when logged in.Email newsletters related cookies This site offers newsletter or email subscription services and cookies may be used to remember if you are already registered and whether to show certain notifications which might only be valid to subscribed/unsubscribed users.Orders processing related cookies This site offers e-commerce or payment facilities and some cookies are essential to ensure that your order is remembered between pages so that we can process it properly.Surveys related cookies From time to time we offer user surveys and questionnaires to provide you with interesting insights, helpful tools, or to understand our user base more accurately. These surveys may use cookies to remember who has already taken part in a survey or to provide you with accurate results after you change pages.Forms related cookies When you submit data to through a form such as those found on contact pages or comment forms cookies may be set to remember your user details for future correspondence.Site preferences cookies In order to provide you with a great experience on this site we provide the functionality to set your preferences for how this site runs when you use it. In order to remember your preferences we need to set cookies so that this information can be called whenever you interact with a page is affected by your preferences.
Third Party Cookies
In some special cases we also use cookies provided by trusted third parties. The following section details which third party cookies you might encounter through this site.
This site uses Google Analytics which is one of the most widespread and trusted analytics solution on the web for helping us to understand how you use the site and ways that we can improve your experience. These cookies may track things such as how long you spend on the site and the pages that you visit so we can continue to produce engaging content. For more information on Google Analytics cookies, see the official Google Analytics page.We also use social media buttons and/or plugins on this site that allow you to connect with your social network in various ways. For these to work the following social media sites including; {List the social networks whose features you have integrated with your site?:12}, will set cookies through our site which may be used to enhance your profile on their site or contribute to the data they hold for various purposes outlined in their respective privacy policies.
More Information
Hopefully that has clarified things for you and as was previously mentioned if there is something that you aren’t sure whether you need or not it’s usually safer to leave cookies enabled in case it does interact with one of the features you use on our site. This Cookies Policy was created with the help of the Cookies Policy Template Generator and the Privacy Policy Template Generator.
However if you are still looking for more information then you can contact us through one of our preferred contact methods:
Email: contact@therealnews.com
This Site Uses Cookies
This site, like many others, uses small files called cookies to help us improve and customize your experience. Learn more about how we use cookies in our cookie policy.
OK
